<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Vaibhav Pujari</title>
    <link>https://vaibhav276.github.io/essays/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Vaibhav Pujari</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vaibhav276.github.io/essays/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Art, Computational and Assisted Creativity</title>
      <link>https://vaibhav276.github.io/essays/posts/art-computational-and-assisted-creativity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vaibhav276.github.io/essays/posts/art-computational-and-assisted-creativity/</guid>
      <description>This is an essay about how I see art, what I think computational creativity is and some things I would like to express about assisted creativity. Before I begin, here is a disclaimer. I am not an artist, neither I am a computer scientist or an Artificial intelligence practitioner. I am just a software engineer, who keeps hearing about these things from various people around me and have thus formed an opinion on these things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>45 Minutes that matter</title>
      <link>https://vaibhav276.github.io/essays/posts/45-minutes-that-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vaibhav276.github.io/essays/posts/45-minutes-that-matter/</guid>
      <description>One of the things that have worked well for me in the past few years of my career is that I have had the good fortune to interact with all kinds of people who applied for a position of software engineer in the company that I work for. While each interview I conduct is different from another in many ways because its dependent on many variables, there is one common thing that I say to the candidate almost every time — that the interview is going to last for about 45 to 60 mins and we will go through some programming exercises during this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My experience with god</title>
      <link>https://vaibhav276.github.io/essays/posts/my-experience-with-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vaibhav276.github.io/essays/posts/my-experience-with-god/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I was a child, I have always found myself questioning the established norms about religion and god. The image of lord Ram with a bow and arrow, lord Krishna with a flute, or lord Ganesha with a elephant head and a bulbous belly are all examples of things that are so natural to one’s imagination. On the evening of Diwali, we used to keep our front door open and light up the whole house hoping for goddess Lakshmi to walk in and bless our home with ceaseless wealth and prosperity and on the evening of Holi, we used to burn the symbol of evil and feel tremendous about it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>